<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DizzyRadio</string>
    <string name="app_name_small">dizzi radio</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="request_a_song">Request a song</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="radio_player">Radio Player</string>
    <string name="now_playing">now playing</string>
    <string name="enjoy_unlimited_music_sensation">Enjoy unlimited music sensation</string>
    <string name="loading">loading...</string>
    <string name="artist_name">artist name</string>
    <string name="listeners">Listeners: </string>
    <string name="not_available">n/a</string>
    <string name="unknown">unknown</string>
    <string name="placeholder">Placeholder</string>
    <string name="song_title">Unknown</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_required">Notification permission is required.</string>
    <string name="go_to_settings">Go to settings</string>
    <string name="about_description"><![CDATA[Dizzy Radio revolutionizes how you experience radio on your Android device. Seamlessly blending convenience with a vast array of content, Dizzy Radio offers an unparalleled radio streaming experience right at your fingertips.\n\nKey Features:\n\nDiscover Your Sound World: Dive into a world of endless audio possibilities with thousands of radio stations spanning genres, languages, and regions. From chart-topping hits to underground gems, Dizzy Radio has something for everyone.\nPersonalized Station Recommendations: Let Dizzy Radio\'s intelligent recommendation engine guide you to new favorites based on your listening habits and preferences. Discover hidden gems and rediscover old classics effortlessly.\nLive Streaming Anytime, Anywhere: Stay connected to your favorite stations with smooth, uninterrupted live streaming. Whether you\'re at home, on the go, or traveling abroad, Dizzy Radio ensures you never miss a beat.\nEasy Navigation & Playback Controls: Effortlessly navigate through stations and control playback with intuitive gestures and controls. Pause, play, skip, and adjust volume with just a tap or swipe.\nCustomize Your Experience: Create personalized playlists, organize favorite stations for quick access, and set alarms to wake up to your favorite morning show or fall asleep to soothing melodies with the built-in sleep timer.\nOffline Listening: Download your favorite shows and podcasts to enjoy offline, perfect for when you\'re commuting, traveling, or in areas with limited internet connectivity.\nSleek & Intuitive Interface: With a clean and intuitive interface designed specifically for Android, Dizzy Radio makes finding and enjoying your favorite stations a breeze. Seamlessly switch between stations and explore new content with ease.\nSocial Sharing: Share your favorite tracks and stations with friends and family on social media platforms directly from the app. Connect with fellow music enthusiasts and discover new content together.\nDizzy Radio is your ultimate companion for exploring the world of radio, offering a rich and immersive experience that caters to your unique tastes and preferences. Whether you\'re a music aficionado, news junkie, or talk show enthusiast, Dizzy Radio brings the best of radio streaming right to your Android device.\n\nDownload Dizzy Radio now and embark on an unforgettable auditory journey!]]></string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_description">Welcome to Dizzy Radio, the radio streaming app. These Terms and Conditions govern your use of the Dizzy Radio mobile application (the \"App\") and its related services. By accessing or using the App, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.\n\n1. Acceptance of Terms\n\nBy using the App, you agree to comply with these Terms and Conditions, our Privacy Policy, and any other guidelines or rules posted on the App. If you do not agree with any part of these terms, you may not use the App.\n\n2. License\n\nWe grant you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to use the App for your personal, non-commercial use only. You may not modify, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information, software, products, or services obtained from the App.\n\n3. User Content\n\nBy using the App, you may have the opportunity to submit, post, or display content, including but not limited to comments, ratings, and reviews (\"User Content\"). You retain ownership of any User Content you submit, but by submitting User Content, you grant us a worldwide, royalty-free, non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such User Content in any media.\n\n4. Privacy\n\nYour privacy is important to us. Please review our Privacy Policy to understand how we collect, use, and disclose information about you.\n\n5. Intellectual Property\n\nThe App, including its content, features, and functionality, is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws. All trademarks, service marks, logos, trade names, and any other proprietary designations are the property of Dizzy Radio or its licensors. Except as expressly provided herein, nothing in these Terms and Conditions shall be construed as conferring any license or right, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, under copyright or other intellectual property rights.\n\n6. Disclaimer of Warranties\n\nThe App is provided on an \"as is\" and \"as available\" basis. We make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, regarding the operation or availability of the App or the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of any information provided through the App.\n\n7. Limitation of Liability\n\nTo the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we shall not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, or any loss of profits or revenues, whether incurred directly or indirectly, or any loss of data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of or inability to access or use the App; (ii) any conduct or content of any third party on the App; (iii) any content obtained from the App; or (iv) unauthorized access, use, or alteration of your transmissions or content.\n\n8. Governing Law\n\nThese Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of [Your Country], without regard to its conflict of law provisions.\n\n9. Changes to Terms and Conditions\n\nWe reserve the right to modify or revise these Terms and Conditions at any time, and such changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the App. Your continued use of the App following the posting of any changes constitutes acceptance of those changes.\n\n10. Contact Us\n\nIf you have any questions about these Terms and Conditions, please contact us at admin@dizzyradio.com.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_description">Welcome to Dizzy Radio, the radio streaming app. Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect information about you when you use the Dizzy Radio mobile application (the \"App\") and its related services. By accessing or using the App, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.\n\n1. Information We Collect\n\nInformation You Provide: When you use the App, you may provide us with information, including but not limited to your name, email address, username, password, and any other information you choose to provide.\nAutomatically Collected Information: We may automatically collect certain information about your device, including your IP address, device type, operating system, unique device identifiers, mobile network information, and information about the way you use the App.\nUsage Data: We may collect information about your interactions with the App, including the radio stations you listen to, the duration of your sessions, and your interactions with features of the App.\n2. How We Use Your Information\n\nWe may use the information we collect for various purposes, including to:\n\nProvide, maintain, and improve the App;\nPersonalize your experience and deliver customized content;\nRespond to your inquiries and provide customer support;\nCommunicate with you about the App and send you updates and notifications;\nMonitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the App;\nDetect, investigate, and prevent fraudulent or unauthorized activity;\nComply with legal obligations.\n3. Sharing of Your Information\n\nWe may share your information with third parties for various purposes, including:\n\nWith service providers who assist us in operating the App and providing related services;\nWith third parties for marketing, advertising, or other promotional purposes, with your consent;\nIn connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets;\nTo comply with legal obligations or protect the rights, property, or safety of Dizzy Radio or others.\n4. Security\n\nWe take reasonable measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure.\n\n5. Your Choices\n\nYou may choose not to provide certain information, but this may limit your ability to use certain features of the App. You can also opt-out of receiving promotional emails from us by following the instructions in those emails.\n\n6. Children\'s Privacy\n\nThe App is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe that we may have collected information from a child under 13, please contact us.\n\n7. Changes to this Privacy Policy\n\nWe reserve the right to update or change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the App. Your continued use of the App following the posting of any changes constitutes acceptance of those changes.\n\n8. Contact Us\n\nIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [contact@email.com].</string>
    <string name="please_provide_artist_name">Please provide artist name</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="please_enter_title">Please enter title</string>
    <string name="genre">Genre</string>
    <string name="please_enter_genre">Please enter genre</string>
    <string name="please_enter_artist_name">Please enter artist name</string>
</resources>